<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="page_odr_proceedings" name="ODR proceedings primer">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div id="wrap">
                <t t-set="bn_nav_inner" t-value="True"/>
                <t t-call="bharatnyay_website.bn_public_nav"/>
                <div class="bn-about-page">
                    <header class="bn-about-hero text-lg-start bn-hero-split">
                        <div class="container">
                            <p class="bn-hash mb-3">Education · Procedures</p>
                            <h1><span class="text-orange">ODR</span> proceeding stages you can orchestrate digitally</h1>
                            <p class="mx-lg-0">From intake to interim relief to final outcome, disciplined case management parallels institutional rules published globally — here translated for NBFC portfolios, enterprise disputes, and court-referred ADR programs.</p>
                        </div>
                    </header>
                    <section class="bn-about-body">
                        <div class="container bn-prose bn-prose-wide">
                            <div class="row gy-5">
                                <div class="col-lg-6">
                                    <h2>1 · Intake &amp; joinder readiness</h2>
                                    <p>Know-your-party checks, claimant onboarding, escrow of supporting debt instruments, tagging related corporate guarantors —
                                        BharatNyay’s vault mirrors best practice registries advocated by arbitration institutions.</p>
                                    <h2 class="mt-4">2 · Procedural timetable</h2>
                                    <p>Deadlines for statements of claim/defence, document production, witness lists, experts — tribunal secretariat dashboards keep defaults visible to both sides (<em>equality of arms</em> shorthand).</p>
                                    <h2 class="mt-4">3 · Interim measures</h2>
                                    <p>Emergency arbitrators / tribunal powers analogous to Sections 9 &amp; 17 interplay — tooling records requests, security for costs postings, conservatory attachments where applicable.</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="col-lg-6">
                                    <h2>4 · Remote hearings etiquette</h2>
                                    <p>Bandwidth tests, oath administration, contempt-safe recording policies, interpreters — BharatNyay’s hearing module aligns with UNCITRAL notes on procedural integrity online.</p>
                                    <h2 class="mt-4">5 · Costs &amp; deposits</h2>
                                    <p>Advance on costs, arbitrator fee mandates, victorious party allocations — surfaced for transparency mandated by tribunal rulesbooks.</p>
                                    <h2 class="mt-4">6 · Settlement homologation</h2>
                                    <p>Mediated settlements can convert into consent awards ; partial settlements bifurcate issues cleanly before final pleadings conclude.</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <p class="mt-4">This lifecycle can run under online mediation, online conciliation, online negotiation, or full arbitration tracks depending on clause design and party consent.</p>
                            <hr class="my-5 opacity-25"/>
                            <div class="d-flex flex-wrap gap-2 justify-content-between align-items-center">
                               
                                <span class="text-muted small mb-2 mb-lg-0">Pair this briefing with BharatNyay’s workflow screens.</span>
                                <div class="d-flex flex-wrap gap-2">
                                    <a href="/odr/model-clause" class="btn btn-primary rounded-pill">Draft clauses →</a>
                                    <a href="/features" class="btn btn-outline-primary rounded-pill">Where software encodes timers</a>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </div>
                <div class="bn-landing-root"><t t-call="bharatnyay_website.bn_public_footer"/></div>
            </div>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>
